Contact

jnarroyo26@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/arroyojulianne (LinkedIn) juliearroyo.com (Personal)

Top Skills HTML5

CSS

SASS

Languages

English

Julianne Arroyo

Web Designer & Developer at O 24 Solutions

San Diego, California

Summary

I'm Julie Arroyo. Builder of websites. Creator of art. Explorer of user science.

Team-oriented Web Designer with 3 years experience creating usable, responsive websites for a wide range of industries. Highly skilled in designing, and developing creative digital experiences for WordPress with a strong focus on delivering exceptional UX.

juliearroyo.com

https://github.com/JulieArroyo

https://www.instagram.com/julie0y0/

Experience

O 24 Solutions
Web Designer / Developer
April 2017 - Present
San Diego

Lead designer & developer at a San Diego marketing start up. I design, build, launch, maintain and provide SEO to client WordPress sites.

Most Common Duties For My Current Role:

- Design new client sites to fit brand specifications
- Optimize current content for web standards & UX/UI standards
- Create & optimize new content when necessary
- Utilizing Adobe Photoshop for logos, client photos & social media posts
- Managing 50+ client WordPress sites
- Providing support & edits for client's existing sites
- Monitor SEO through Google Analytics
- Handling domain transfers (DNS & CNAME Management)
- Launching an average of 3 newly created sites per month.

Web Domain Solutions

Web Developer

December 2016 - April 2017 (5 months)

San Diego, CA

Front End Developer and SEO Manager at Web Domain Solutions

- Hand Coded websites using a custom CMS
- Write compelling copy for clients
- Manage any sort of maintenance throughout the life of the websites
- Started SEO maintenance & optimization program for each client site
- Set up Google Plus and any other social media accounts to clients that requested so.

Okun Enterprises

Graphic Designer

June 2016 - November 2016 (6 months)

San Diego, California

- Worked with the marketing team to create everything from print to web.
- Created website design as well as logos, flyers, business cards, billboards & more.

TMP Worldwide

Inbound Marketing Intern

October 2015 - January 2016 (4 months)

Chicago, IL

Interning for TMP Worldwide I learned a lot about digital marketing and social media management.

- Worked within the Inbound Marketing team to create compelling Careers pages for major companies
- Translated site copy to HTML and CSS for content pages
- Optimized the pages for SEO & mobile responsiveness
- Organize our companies site pages to get ready for a new website

Seattle University

Student

January 2015 - December 2015 (1 year)

Seattle WA

Graduated from the Front-End Web Development certificate program at Seattle University in 2015.

Education

Seattle University
Web Development · (2015 - 2016)

Highland High School (2003 - 2007)

Ivy Tech Community College